scop.io 2019-05-16

# Scopio Privacy Policy

**This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) tells you about our online collection and use of data. Scopio is committed to protecting your privacy. By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This site is owned by Scopio Technologies, Inc. (“Scopio”) and may be accessed in the United States and abroad.**  
  
 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM THIS WEBSITE.** We collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit the site and input information, whether you are registering to use the site, enrolling or signing up for features and functions, ordering or purchasing visual media content or, in the course of any other exchanges of information, transactions and activities. We may use the information we obtain from you, including personally identifiable information, to tailor your experience on the site, to display content we think may be of interest to you or to let us customize what you see when you visit the site, according to your preferences.

When you visit this web site, some information may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation, such as your IP and email addresses as well as navigational details. Your name, postal address, phone number, email address, password and other information are collected when you register online with Scop.io

If you wish to use the Scopio Services or license content from Scopio’s Marketplace your username, password, full name, telephone number, e-mail address and postal address, your credit card number and other personally identifying information is collected to complete the license agreement or to receive visual media content, products or services. On occasions, we may use certain account information such as credit card number and company information of authorized users to conduct credit inquiries.   

From time to time Scopio may ask you questions about you or questions which might relate to your user preferences. This information may be linked to your personal information. Providing this kind of information is always voluntary. Scopio also collects your orders, your searches and selections and other account information as part of your sales history with us. We do this in order to better serve you and improve the use of the Scopio website and platform. We may also compile data in aggregate form so that we may better understand the users that are visiting our website. 

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT.**  We may use information in any of the following ways: 

  1. For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify orders for visual media content. 
  2. To send you email notifications about our new or existing services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
  3. To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and websites.
  4. To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.
  5. To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

We may combine the information that we collect from you on the site with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products or websites. 

We may hire other companies to provide services on our behalf including, without limitation, facilitating some aspects of the web site, sending e-mail and fulfilling purchase requests. These other companies may be supplied with or have access to your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf.   

We may use third parties (called third-party ad servers or ad networks) to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third-party ad servers may be supplied with or have access to your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf. They also may also collect and use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the web site and other websites in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you.   

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of Scopio unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us.   

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Service and Licensing Agreement (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights). 

**E-MAIL MESSAGES.** If you register on our website, you may occasionally receive email messages about the website that are intended to assist you in making the most out of your registration. Such email messages may contain a link that you may use to “opt-out” of receiving further such messages.   
  
**COOKIES.** Scopio uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect can include the date and time of your visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase history. Cookies are not linked to you as an individual and cannot be used to track where you have been either before or after you visit.   
  
Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can retrieve previous image search results, access lightboxes and view their previous invoices. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.   

Most browsers allow you to decline cookies, but if you elect to do so, certain pages and user features such as lightboxes may not display properly. You are free to delete cookies after your session. Your browser should contain instructions on how to do this.   

**ADS FOR THIS WEBSITE.** When you view an ad for this web site on other sites, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The web site and our advertising company may also use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) to note which web site pages you visit after viewing our ads. Once again, the information that is collected through the use of these visual media content is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts.   
  
**DATA SECURITY.** We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information and while no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used, and will continue to use, commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your information. We continually assess new technology for protecting information and, when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.   
  
**REVIEWING, UPDATING OR CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION.  **If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may inform us at [info@Scop.io](mailto:info@Scop.io)    
  
 **LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES.** We may link to web sites, including those of our subsidiaries and content providers that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.   
  
**CHILDREN.** Scopio does not intend to either solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you should not use or enter information on this website.   
  
**CHANGES TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY.** Scopio reserves the right to modify its privacy policy at any time without notice. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this web site will be deemed conclusive acceptance of such modification. 

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER.** We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on our website. If you have any questions about Scopio's privacy policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to Scop.io, please contact Scopio’s Customer Service at [info@Scop.io](mailto:info@Scop.io)

**GOVERNING LAW.** This Agreement shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of the State of New York, regardless of the laws that might otherwise govern under applicable principles of conflicts of laws. In any action or suit between any of the parties arising out of or relating to this Agreement: (a) each of the parties irrevocably and unconditionally consents and submits to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of New York, or if such court does not have proper jurisdiction, then the federal courts located in the State of New York, and appellate courts therefrom (collectively, the New York Courts); and (b) each of the parties irrevocably waives the right to trial by jury.

**USERS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES:**

By visiting Scopio, submitting information or using the website, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and consent to having your data transferred to and processed in the United States.  If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use Scop.io, Shop.Scop.io or Scopio services.

Scopio is controlled and operated from the United States.  Scopio does not represent or warrant that Scop.io, Shop.Scop.io or any part thereof, are appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access Scopio do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. 

You are also subject to United States export controls in connection with your use of Scopio’s and/or services related thereto and are responsible for any violations of such controls, including, without limitation, any United States embargoes or other federal rules and regulations restricting exports. 

Scopio may limit the availability of Scopio’s services, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction that Scopio chooses, at any time and in Scopio’s sole discretion.
